Exercise 6-14, Tandem Reading. The last reading that I'd like you to do is one
along with me. Up to now, I've read first and you've repeated in the pause that
followed. Now, however, I'd like you to read along at exactly the same time that I
read so that we sound like one person reading. Hello, my name is Anne. I'm
taking American accent training. Read along with me. Hello, my name is Anne. I'm
taking American accent training. There's a lot to learn, but I hope to make it as
enjoyable as possible. I should pick up on the American intonation pattern pretty
easily, although the only way to get it is to practice all the time. I use the up and
down or peaks and valleys intonation more than I used to. I've been paying attention
to pitch, too. It's like walking down a staircase. I've been talking to a lot of
Americans lately, and they tell me that I'm easier to understand. Anyway, I could
go on and on, but the important thing is to listen well and sound good. Well, what
do you think? Do I?